CESAR NAVARRO

PROGRAMMER JR



CONTACT

- 55 4489 7723
- O COACALCO, MEXICO
- GITHUB.COM/RASECKSHOW

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- C/C++
- Java
- C#
- Javascript
- SQL

••••

••••

LANGUAGES

- Spanish
- English

•••••

PROFILE

Computer engineering student interested in new technologies. During my studies I became passionate about software development. With the intention of joining the industry taking advantage of my ability to analyze a problem and find the best possible solution, as well as provide a pleasant digital experience to the user.

EXPERIENCE

DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR (BOOTCAMP)

ORACLE NEXT EDUCATION | FEBRUARY 2021 - MAY 2022

- Database queries (MySQL).
- Data manipulation.
- Role administration.

DEVELOPER FULL-STACK (BOOTCAMP)

ORACLE NEXT EDUCATION | AUGUST 2023 - JANUARY 2023

- Creation and styling of responsive web pages.
- Creation and validation of forms.
- Connection to database, CRUD.

PROGRAMMER JAVASCRIPT (TITLING PROJECT)

CECYT NO 8 NARCISO BASSOLS | AUGUST 2016 - DECEMBER 2016

- Creation of scripts for movement, mini-map and interaction with the environment.
- Work team management.

PROGRAMMER BACKEND (TITLING PROJECT)

CECYT NO 8 NARCISO BASSOLS | AUGUST 2016 - DECEMBER 2016

- Database connection (MySQL).
- Programming of website components.
- Server configuration.

EDUCATION

DEVELOPER FULL-STACK

ORACLE NEXT EDUCATION ALURA LATAM | 2022 - 2023

COMPUTER ENGINEERING

INTERDISCIPLINARY PROFESSIONAL UNIT OF ENGINEERING, SOCIAL AND ADMINISTRATIVE SCIENCES IPN | 2017 - IN PROGRESS

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN

CECYT NO. 8 NARCISO BASSOLS, IPN | 2013 - 2016